对  新皮夹
Hey! New wallet, huh?
也该换新的了  里面的安全套终于不再说"好凉快"了
Yeah, It was time. The old condom ring in the leather just doesn't say 'cool' anymore.
瑞秋  你把吃剩的空盒子又放回冰箱
Rachel, you just put an empty carton back in the fridge.
对啊  因为垃圾袋满了
I know, but the garbage was full.
你从来没有倒过垃圾吗
Have you ever taken out the trash?
我以为这是你的爱好
Well, I thought you liked doing it.
左边第三个门   知道了
Third door on the left. Right!
（垃圾槽）
嗨  崔戈先生
Hey, Mr. Treeger.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
对不起
I'm sorry.
虽然不那么新鲜  不过...
It's a little old but…
不是说这个  你堵住了我花半小时才弄通的垃圾道
No! You're clogging up the chute that I spent a half-hour unclogging!
真对不起  我不常来
I'm sorry.  I didn't—I don't come in here a lot.
是啊  你当然不常来  因为你是个小公主
Oh yeah, of course you don't! 'Cause you're a little princess!
爸爸  给我买份披萨
Daddy, buy me a pizza.
爸爸  给我买个糖果厂
Daddy, buy me a candy factory.
爸爸  让猫咪们为我唱生日歌
Daddy, make the cast of Cats sing "Happy Birthday" to me.
你以为你可以到这儿来
You think you can come here...
搞得一团糟  反正最后穿工装的大个子会来清扫
make a mess and the big man in coveralls will come in here and clean it up, huh?
为什么不替他人多想想  改一改呢
Well, why don't think of someone else for a change?
哦  我很抱歉
Okay, I'm sorry.
老天  干这么点活你也会哭
God, if you're going to cry about it!
《老友记》  第四季  第04集  与郎共舞
Friends S04E04  The one with the ballroom dancing
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
是崔戈把你弄哭的
Whoa, whoa! Treeger made you cry?
是啊  他说话相当刻薄  而且并非都是真的
Yes! And he said really mean things that were only partly true.
我要下去给那家伙上一课  教训他一下
I'm gonna go down there and teach that guy a lesson.
乔伊  别去  我们最好忘掉这事
Joey, please don't do that. I think it's best that we just forget about it.
你说的倒轻松  刚才被折磨的又不是你
That's easy for you to say. You weren't almost just killed!
好的  上课的时间到了
All right, that's it. School is in session!
天啊  这是健身卡吗
My God! Is this a gym card?
哦  没错  健身房会员
Oh, yeah, gym member.
我原打算每周去四次  但我错过了...
I try to go four times a week, but I've missed the last...
最后1200次
1200 times.
为什么不退出
So why don't you quit?
你以为我没试过吗
You don't think I've tried?
你以为他们每月从我帐户上扣掉50块  我很开心吗
You think I like having 50 dollars taken out of my bank account every month?
不  他们让你到他们那里
No, they make you go all the way down there!
然后就运用所有的词语和表情来迷惑你
Then they use all of these phrases and peppiness to try and confuse you!
最后他们推出了玛利亚
And then they bring out Maria.
玛利亚是谁  哦  玛利亚
Who is Maria? Oh, Maria!
你没有能力拒绝她
You can't say no to her.
她就像是用合成弹力纤维包装的健身房的...礼品
she's like this lycra spandex covered gym…treat.
要我和你一道去帮你打气吗
Do you need me to go with you and hold your hand?
不用了  那你有勇气单独面对她吗
No!  So you're strong enough to face her on your own?
不  你还是来吧
Oh no, you'll have to come.
崔比亚尼  等一下
Tribbiani. Hold on.
我去拿皮揣子 (通马桶用)
I'll get the plunger.
你等一下伙计  你把我朋友瑞秋气哭了
You hold on pal! Now you made my friend, Rachel, cry.
你得上去向她道歉
So now, you're gonna go up there and apologize to her...
否则我就要去找房东了
unless you want me to call the landlord.
跟他说什么
And tell him what?
你难道不知道什么叫 "不准让女孩哭泣"吗
Have you heard about a little something called "not making girls cry."
你也许听过1968年发布的《租屋安定法案》吧
Yeah. Well maybe you have heard about the Rent Stabilization Act of 1968!
说实话  我还真的没听过
I have actually not heard of that.
你朋友触犯了这个法案
Yeah, well your friends are in violation of it.
我一直没出声  不过现在我不用再做好人了
I've been a nice guy up until now, but, I don't need this grief.
我要去告诉房东
I'm gonna call the landlord...
把莫妮卡外婆的房子转租给她  是非法的
and tell him that Monica is illegally subletting here grandmother's apartment.
你的朋友们要被赶出去了  伙计
Your friends are out of here, pal.
你为什么不告诉我些  我不知道的东西
Why don't you tell me something I don't know!
拜托  今天我真不想去上班
Oh please, somebody tell me I don't have to go to work today!
怎么了
What's the matter?
今天第一个客人是个帅得一塌糊涂的家伙
My first massage today is this incredibly gorgeous guy.
一看到他  我就想...
and every time I see him I just want to...
替他免费服务一下
do things to him that I'm not allowed to charge for.
那就免费吧
So do them for free.
不行  公司不准
No, it is forbidden.
跟客人乱来  会被波特太太开除
No-no, Mrs. Potter fires people for fooling around with clients.
而且也违反女按摩师的誓言
And it's against my oath as a masseuse.
你们要宣誓的吗  不  我自己的誓言
They make you take an oath? No, I made myself take an oath.
不得与客人乱来...
Yeah, no fooling around with clients...
时刻准备着
and always be prepared.
后一句是童子军说的  不过说得通
Yeah, that one's actually from the Boy Scouts, but it just makes good sense.
你为什么不把他转给别人
Why don't you just give him to somebody else?
不用  我能处理  我是职业的
No, I can handle it. No, I'm a professional.
菲比  那是个新脚镯吗
Oh Pheebs, is that a new ankle bracelet?
你还做了脚部美容  还盛装打扮
And you got a petticure. Your feet are all dressed up.
因为当他在按摩台上  那是你唯一能被他看见的部分
Because that's the only part of you he can see when he's on the table!
你想用脚来勾引他
You're gonna do some feet flirting!
我不懂你们在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
那脚趾环你又怎么解释
Then how do you explain the toe ring?!
因为今天是阿拉伯公主日  行了吧  别烦我
Because it's Arabian princess day at work! Okay?! Leave me alone!
英雄  事情怎样了
My hero! What happened?
我下去告诉他  说谁也不能那样对我朋友
Well, I went down there and told him that no one treats my friends like that.
最好能上来道个歉  待会儿见
and that he'd better come up here and apologize. I'll see you later.
等等
Wait a minute.
那他怎么说
What did he say?
他说他不会来道歉  因为你们住在这里是违法的
He said that he wasn't gonna apologize because you guys are living here illegally.
相反他要把你们赶出去  待会儿见
so instead what he's gonna do is have you evicted-I'll see you later.
什么  你搞到我们要被赶出去  告诉过你不要去
What?! You got us evicted! I told you not to go down there!
他把瑞秋气哭了
He made Rachel cry!
瑞秋经常哭的
Rachel always cries!
这不是真的吧
That's not true!
现在你得去拍他的马屁
You go down there and you suck up to him
而且要拍得不留痕迹
I mean you suck like you've never sucked before!
好吧  我试试看
All right, I'll try.
不过失败的话  你们可以和钱德还有我暂时一起住着
But if I can't, you can stay with Chandler and I until you get settled.
快去   好...
Go! All right, all right.
我会先和他商量商量  不过我想他可能会很酷
I mean I'll have to check with him first, but I'll think he'll be cool with it.
记着我们刚才说过的  你要强硬一点
Now remember what we talked about, you gotta be strong.
是的  是的
Yes! Yes!
再试一次
One more time.
"嗨  你不想拥有平滑的小腹和结实的胸肌吗"
"Hey, don't you want a washboard stomach and rock hard pecs?"
不  我要的是松弛的肚皮和下垂的胸部
No! I want a flabby gut and saggy man breasts!
好  非常好
Good! That's good.
我想要退出健身房
I want to quit the gym.
你要退出
You want to quit?
我要退出健身房
I want to quit the gym.
知道吗  你将因此不能享受新推出的全套瑞式温泉浴服务
You do realize that you won't have access to our new full service Swedish spa.
我要退出健身房
I want to quit the gym.
好吧  戴夫在会员资格办公室里负责办理退会
Okay, Dave in the membership office, handles quitters.
对不起  你是会员吗
Excuse me. Are you a member?
我
Me?
不是
No!
对不起  只有会员能进去
Sorry. Members only.
我要退出健身房
I want to quit the gym!
没事的老兄  要强硬
It's okay, man. Be strong.
你参加过健身房吗
So, are you a member of any gym.
没有  也没这个打算  你不用白费唇舌了
No! And I'm not gonna be, so you can save you little speech.
好的  没问题
Okay, no problem.
你能过来一下吗
Could you come here for a second?
嗨  我是玛利亚
Hi, I'm Maria.
你的脚真漂亮
You have really pretty feet.
都是些旧玩意儿
These old things.
你能帮我按一按髋部吗  痛了我一整天了
Would you mind spending some time on my siadic area, it's been killing me today.
你指...
You mean the...
髋部  你指...
Okay by siadic, you mean the...
毛巾盖着的这部分
towel-covered portion?
当然  没问题
Sure, yeah, no I can do that, yeah.
因为髋部的肌肉通常很
because, you know, the muscles in the siadic area can get you know...
结实而且美观
real nice and tight.
告诉我里克  你怎么会弄伤这里的
So tell me, Rick, how did you injure the area?
为了绿色和平组织16个钟头的静坐抗议
A 16-hour sit-in for Greenpeace.
你刚才咬了我  没有
Did you just bite me? No!
怎样
What?
拜托不要把莫妮卡和瑞秋赶出去  不是她们的错  错在我
Please don't kick Monica and Rachel out, this wasn't there fault, it was mine.
你是要我把你们赶出去
You want me to kick you guys out instead?
你不能这么做  那样小鸡小鸭该住哪儿
No you can't do that, where would the chick and the duck live?
你们养宠物  没  没有
You have pets? No! no!
那些只是外号
Those are nicknames.
我是"小鸡"   钱德是"小鸭"
I'm the "chick," and Chandler's the "duck."
我还以为你是"小鸭"
I would've thought it was the other way around.
求求你  只要让她们留下来
Come on man, just-just let the girls stay.
我帮你做什么都行
I'll do whatever you want.
真的  什么都行
Really? You'd do anything?
是  我保证
Yeah, absolutely.
倒真有点事你能帮忙
Yeah, I've got something you can do.
什么事
What is it?
你能做我的舞伴吗
Can you be my dancing partner?
这不是监狱里的黑话吧
That's not prison lingo, is it?
他的舞伴
His dancing partner?
有个公寓主管的舞会  主管(超级)舞会
Yeah, there's this superintendent's dance "The Super Ball."
他想引起玛芝的注意  就是他爱上的那个女主管
and he wants to impress Marge, this lady super that he's a crush on.
为什么不找个女生来练习
Well, why doesn't he practice with a girl?
他太怕羞
Well, he's too shy
以他现在的技术  还不能和女生跳舞
He doesn't thing he's good enough to dance with girls yet.
那倒没错
Yeah, right.
他差点让我跳进那个垃圾道
He almost danced me right down that garbage chute.
你还没忘  又不是什么大事
Would you let it go already? You're fine.
你退出了吗
So, did you quit?
我都快成功了
No, I almost did.
可我不能让罗斯在那儿没伴儿啊
couldn't leave Ross there without a spotter!
等等  现在  你参加了健身
Wait, now so you joined the gym?
好笑吗  笑什么
And that's funny, why?
我只是在想象你精疲力尽的模样  还有...
I was just, you know, picturing you working out, and...
哦  没什么了
Well, that's it.
我们没救了
We're doomed. Okay,
在我们的余生中  他们将每月从我们帐户里扣掉50块
They're gonna take 50 bucks out of our accounts for the rest of our lives.
该怎么办
What are we gonna do?
你们可以真的去健身
Well, you could actually go to the gym.
或者  我们可以去银行
Or we could go to the bank...
销掉帐户  切断他们的来源
close our accounts and cut them off at the source.
你真是天才
You're a genius.
老兄  那我们就不再是帐户的合伙人了
Oh, man! But then, we won't be bank buddies.
又多了一条理由
Now there's two reasons.
你们还记得我上次提到的那个帅哥顾客吗
You guys, remember that cute client I told you about?
我咬了他
I bit him.
哪里  屁股
Where? On the tushy.
这不违背你的誓言吗
And that's not against your oath?
我知道  我很抱歉  可是当我一摸他
No, I know! I'm sorry, but the moment I touch him
我就想抛开旧誓言  发一个限制级的新誓言
I just wanna throw out my old oath and take a new, dirty one.
下次按摩  试着分散自己的注意力
Well, next time your massaging him, you should try and distract yourself.
像我在做让我很兴奋的事
Yeah! Yeah! like when I'm doing something exciting...
而我又不想让自己太
and I don't wanna get too...
兴奋
excited.
我就想点其他的  像...三明治
I just, you know try to thing of other things like ah sandwiches...
棒球
and baseball...
钱德
and Chandler.
乔伊  多谢你  不  不  该我谢你
Thank you, Joey. Oh, no, thank you.
我想尽快把事情办完
All right, I'm here. Let's get this over with.
好的
Okay, well...
跟着我的舞步
just follow my lead.
不需要先做点准备吗
Don't we need to do some kind of preparation first?
比如  喝个烂醉
Like get really drunk?
来  用手环抱着我
Come on. Hey, just put your arms around me.
真对不起
I'm sorry.
不要紧  不过要是玛芝
No. It's okay. But if I'm Marge...
我的胸要从背部出来了
my breasts are coming out my back.
算了  我永远也跳不好
Forget it! I'm not being any good at this.
我妈说的对
My mom was right.
我只是个有头  有手  有脚的大土豆
I'm just a big potato with arms and legs and a head.
老兄  你并不是什么土豆
Come on, man. You're not a potato.
我不适合跳舞  练也没用
I'm sure as hell not a dancer. It's no use.
玛姬不会看上我的
Marge will never go for me.
别这么说  崔戈
Come on, Treeger. Don't say that.
你只要多练练
You just need more practice.
来  我们再试一次
Here, Come on. Let's try it again.
刚才可能要怪我
Plus, it was probably mostly my fault anyway.
你知道  我不是个让人感觉很舒服的舞伴...
I mean, you know, I'm not really that comfortable dancing with a...
舞练得怎样  像在"搞同性恋"吗
So how goes the dancing? Gay yet?
你们这次要多谢我
You guys owe me bigtime.
什么
What was that?
你刚才在跳舞
You just did a little dancy thing.
我没有  你跳了
No, I didn't. Yes, you did.
刚才跳了两下   跳得很开心
You did like a little hop.You are soo enjoying this.
没有  我没有
No, I'm not.
那不是跳   那是帕得玛利舞
And it wasn't a hop it was a pademarie.
术语你都知道
You know the words!
你真的很投入
You are so into this!
可能我开始有点喜欢跳舞了  其实我已经跳得相当不错
All right, well maybe I'm enjoying it a little bit. I mean I'm getting pretty good at it.
真棒  舞姿翩翩的小乔伊
This is so sweet. Joey, our little twinkletoes.
这可不是女孩子跳的那种舞
Hold on, this isn't some kind of like girly dance.
它像一种体育运动  很阳刚的
All right, it's like a sport, it's manly!
来  秀几个阳刚的舞步  好
All right, then show me some manly moves. All right.
我不会带舞
I don't know how to lead.
你好
Hello.
我们想要销户
We'd like to close our accounts.
销户  出了什么问题吗
Close your accounts? Is there some kind of problem?
我们只是想销户
No, we'd just like to close them.
销户是由兰伯特女士办理的
Okay, Ms. Lambert handles all our closures.
请过来  这边好吗
Would you come over here please?
嗨  我叫凯伦
Hi, I'm Karen.
我要退出银行
I want to quit the bank!
好吧  棒球
Okay. Baseball.
里克是打棒球的  滑上二垒
Rick playing baseball. He slides into second.
要是他的短裤也滑下去一点儿
Maybe even his pants come down a little.
不行  不行  等等...
No, no, wait...
好吧  三明治  三明治
Okay, sandwiches. Sandwiches.
装在盘子里的
Okay, on a plate.
要是里克的短裤滑下去一点儿
Maybe Rick's pants come down a little.
钱德
Chandler.
钱德  这个有效
Okay, Chandler. That's working!
钱德的膝盖
Chandler's knees.
钱德的脚脖子
Chandler's ankles.
钱德脚脖子上的毛
Chandler's ankle hair.
哦  老天
Oh, no!
全部做完了
Okay, you're all set.
哇  真不敢相信
Wow! That was amazing!
只过了一个小时吗   是的
Was that really just an hour? Yeah.
这里的一小时真长啊
In really long-hour world.
什么
What?
我迷上你了
I have an enormous crush on you.
但因为你是顾客  我不能约你
But because you're a client, I can't ask you out...
尽管你让我有...这种感觉
even though you give me you know, the feeling.
我根本不知道
I had no idea.
不过  我可以找别人帮我按摩
But you know, I could always find another masseuse.
真的
Really?
对  真的
Yeah, really.
怎么了
What?
突然间很不习惯我光着身子
Suddenly I'm very aware I'm naked.
乖乖躺下吧
Okay, quit down.
西蒙先生已经等了...哦   我的天
Mr. Simors been waiting for...Oh, my God!
为什么刚才没给我提供这个
Why wasn't I offered that?
我肯定会多给些钱的
I'd definitely pay more for that.
菲比  这里有规定  这里不是那种地方
Phoebe, we have rules here, this isn't that kind of place.
我知道  但不是像你想的那样
Oh yeah, oh and I know, but this isn't what it looks like...
因为里克是...我老公
because Rick is my...husband.
哦  是吗
Oh, really?
你最好先告诉他的另一个老婆
Well, then you'd better tell his other wife
她已经打了三次电话来问他在哪里
because she called three times asking where he is.
好的  我会告诉她的
Yes, I will tell her.
你们最后没有销户
So you didn't leave the bank?
是的  而且最后我们合开了一个支票帐户
No! And somehow, we ended up with a joint checking account.
开那个干什么
What are you ever gonna use that for?!
转帐给健身中心
To pay for the gym.
我今天过的真不错
So I had a great day.
里克和我一拍即合  我们正想更进一步
Rick and I really hit it off, and we started making out,
老板就走了进来  以为我是个妓女  开除了我
and then my boss walked in and fired me for being a whore.
你被开除了  我的天
You got fired? Oh, my gosh!
真不敢相信  我以前从没因为任何原因被开除过
It's so weird, I have never been fired from anything before!
亲爱的
Sweetie.
我只好漫无目的四处游荡
I just started walking around not knowing what to do next.
问街上的人是否需要按摩
I started asking people on the street if they wanted massages.
结果警察也认为我是个妓女
Then these policemen, thought I was a whore too
真是倒霉的一天  妓女式的
It's really been a bad day, whore-wise.
嗨  小鸭  小鸡在吗
Hey, Duck. Is Chick here?
在...兔宝宝
Yeah, Bunny Rabbit.
这是最后一次练习  准备好了吗
So you, ready for our last practice?
我觉得转圈还不够好
Yeah, but you know, I think the reason we're not getting that spin right is
因为我那里太小了
because my apartment's too small.
那你想用我们的房子吗  不  我另有办法
Look, you wanna use our place? No, I had another idea.
成功了
We did it!
我们做到了 难以置信  太棒了
I know, we did it!! Hey, that was incredible, huh?!
太精彩了  非常完美  我们完全固定住了
That was amazing! I mean, we totally nailed it, it was beautiful.
谢谢你  真的很感谢你  崔比亚尼
Hey, listen. Thanks a lot, Tribbiani.
老天  时间到了
Oh, my God! Look at the time.
我得赶公交车去舞会了
I got to catch the bus to the ball.
祝你好运
Good luck.
你还想再练练狐步舞吗  或者探戈
Unless you wanna practice the Foxtrot again? Or-or the Tango?
谢谢  不过不必了
Thanks, but no.
我觉得我可以开始和女生跳了
You see, I think I'm ready to dance with girls.
快去吧  崔戈  好
Go get them, Treeger. Right.
要不要一道去  玛芝有个女朋友
You want to come? Marge has a girlfriend.
真的  没错
Really? Yeah!
你可以和她好好跳跳  她个头和我差不多
You could dance real good with her, she's the same size as me.
哦  不用了
No, I'm good.
看来你很有工作经验
So it looks like you've got some great experience here.
上一份工作为什么没做下去呢
Let's see, reason for leaving last job?
他们以为我是个妓女
Yeah, they thought I was a whore.
好吧  如果有消息我们会通知你的
Okay, we'll give a call if anything comes up.
太好了  非常感谢
Great! Thank you very much.